fumikomu ze akuseru
press down hard on the gas
kakehiki wa nai sa sou dayo
that's right, there's no compromise
yoru wo nukeru
we'll slip through the night
nejikomu sa saigo ni
at the final moment push hard
sashihiki zero sa sou dayo
that's right, all the way to zero
hibi wo kezuru
until we wipe away the days
kokoro wo sotto
gently open your heart
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
if you pull it close to you
todoku yo kitto
it will reach you, without a doubt
tsutau yo motto sa aa
it will come, closer, now
iki isoide shiboritotte
we're speeding through life, squeezing it for all of its worth
motsureru ashi
our feet are tied
dakedo mae yori zutto sou tooku he
but we still keep going further
ubaitotte tsukandatte
even if I take it back, and grasp it
kimi janai nara
if you're not the one
imi wa nai no sa
there will be no meaning
dakara haruka kanata
and so we'll go far off into the distance
We now start the second test
of the Chunin Exam!
Look for the brats!
Those three, right?
All right! Let's go!
Okay! First we search for that thing.
Can you do it, Hinata?
Yes.
Slow down, Lee! We just started.
I know. But...
I can't stay still!
Who knows what kind of
powerful foe is waiting for us?!
As you already understand,
we have only one target!
It sounds like they've already started.
Huh? That was someone's
scream just now, right?
I-I'm kinda getting nervous.
I-It was nothing, Sakura-chan.
I-I have to pee.
Y-You... Fool!
What are you doing in front of a lady!
Go to the grass!
Eat or be Eaten!
Naruto Becomes Bait
Oh...! Oh...!
Ahhh... that was a lot!
Feels much better!
C'mon Naruto! I told you not to say
things like that in front of a lady...!
What?!
S-Sasuke-kun...
no matter what,
you don't have to go that far.
W-What was that for?
Where's the real Naruto?!
Huh?
I don't know what the hell
you're talking about!
What happened to the scratch
you got earlier from the Proctor?!
And... your Shuriken holster
is on your left leg.
That guy's right-handed.
You're worse at transformation
than Naruto, you phony!
Unlucky me! In that case...
Which one of you got the scroll?!
Since things have come to this,
I'll resort to force!
Fire Style:
Phoenix Flower Jutsu!
Hey! Sasuke!
You've got to be kidding, useless.
All right!
I caught you off guard! Lucky!
Paper Bomb...!
This is lucky!
I'll kill you if you move!
Calmly hand over the scroll!
Sasuke-kun!
I won't let you get away!
Y-You're always late Naruto!
Absorption with my Chakra.
Sasuke-kun...
Don't just stand there, Sakura!
No guarantee this guy's alone!
Got it?!
If you let your guard down
you'll really get killed...
It's unlucky! I came on my own
to conceal my presence,
but that became my enemy...
He got away, huh...?
If there's an instance that
we become separated,
don't trust him if he looks
like your teammate.
Just like now there's a possibility
that an enemy will transform
to get close to us!
— Yeah.
— So what do we do?
We'll decide on a password.
Password?
Listen, if the password is incorrect,
no matter what he looks like...
presume he is an enemy!
I'll only say it once, so listen closely.
You ask,
Ninja song, "Ninja Chance."
And the answer is this:
"The chance to sneak up when a large
number of enemies are making a scene.
"The quiet place has no secret hideout.
"It is important for a Shinobi
to know the right time.
"The time when an enemy is tired
and drops his guard."
That's it.
Okay!
Could you say it again?
Huh?!
I told you I'd only say it once.
Could it be that you couldn't memorize it?
— You fool!
— Huh?!
I got it right away!
I-I memorized it perfectly!
I thought just in case,
I'd listen one more time...
I'll carry the scroll!
Hey, wait Sasuke.
Ouch!
What is it?
A new enemy?!
You guys go play around ...
I'll go alone...
Sakura!
Sasuke-kun!
Don't come closer!
First the password...
Ninja song, "Ninja Chance"!
Ah! Umm...
The chance to sneak up where a large
number of enemies are making a scene.
The quiet place has no secret hideout.
It is important for a Shinobi
to know the right time.
The time when an enemy is tired
and drops his guard.
Good.
Ow!
Hey everyone, are you okay?
Naruto, wait!
The password...
I know...
The chance to sneak up where a large
number of enemies are making a scene.
The quiet place has no
secret hideout.
It is important for a Shinobi
to know the right time.
The time when an enemy
is tired and drops his guard.
— What?!
— Huh?!
What are you doing?!
This time it's someone who
can dodge my attack, huh?
What are you saying, Sasuke-kun?
Naruto just said
the password properly.
He was able to say it,
that's the problem!
— Huh?!
— Wha...?
Do you really think that guy can
remember a password that long?
Oh!
If we asked the normal Naruto
what the password is,
what do you think he'd say?
"Sorry. I've forgotten it."
Besides, his movements when
he avoided my attack...
It was clearly different
from Naruto's!
Show your true self already,
fake one!
That's how it is, huh...
But if you knew he would forget it,
why didn't you make
the password shorter?
I knew that you were
underground
eavesdropping on
our conversation.
So I chose that password on purpose.
Oh really. So you're not tired
or letting your guard down.
This will be more fun than I thought.
This person's... too creepy!
And where's Naruto?
Huh?
Ow!
And heave!
Huh? Where are Sakura-chan
and that Sasuke?
H-Huge!
This is the first time I've seen...
a snake this huge!
Behind?!
T-Tail!
You want our Earth Scroll,
don't you?
‘Cause you have the Heaven Scroll.
Well, let's begin...
the battle for the Scrolls.
Life or Death!
Genjutsu?!
No, that's not it.
This is simply
a thirst for blood.
What's going on?
Just looking at her eyes
made me think of death.
Who is this... woman?!
Sa... Sakura...?
It's no good.
We have no choice but to flee here.
Unless we do, the only thing
waiting for us is...
Death!
Let me out! Hey!
Spit... me... out!
Damn!
It's not going to work.
Something else...
Oh!
The rice ball I took for lunch!
Huh?!
It's dissolving!
I'll be digested just like
that rice ball eventually...
N-No!
Let me out! Let me... out!
Can't move already...?
She's going to kill me!
Move... move... move...!
Move!
Move! Move!
Even if it's just a little...
Move!
What do you intend to do... with that?
I can't move!
Don't worry.
I'll end this in a second.
You won't even have
the time to feel pain.
I wanted you to entertain me more.
It's too bad.
Am... I going to die here?
Iruka-sensei
Old Man Hokage...
Konohamaru...
Kakashi-sensei.
Sakura-chan.
Sasuke.
A lot happened between him and me.
Even though we always squabbled,
we cooperated and saved Kakashi-sensei
in that encounter with Zabuza.
During our Chakra training in the forest,
we competed against each other and
practiced climbing up trees.
That's it! I haven't...
settled things with him yet!
— More rice!
If this creature doesn't want to
spit me out ...
I'll make it to do so at any cost!
I see.
Sasuke-kun!
He wounded himself
at the last moment...
Move. Move. Move.
Move...!
Move!
He wiped out the fear with pain.
As expected,
he's not the average prey.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
I... am a Shinobi who
will become Hokage!
I won't put up with being
snake dung in this place!
Sasuke-kun.
Are you okay?
If we don't flee in a hurry,
we'll be discovered here, too.
How do we flee...?
How should we escape...?
I've never seen Sasuke-kun...
so worked up.
Sasuke-kun, a snake!
Shoot! I was too shaken up
to notice the snake!
Don't come near me!
Don't lower your guard,
not even for a moment...
A prey must always stay tense
and try to flee desperately...
before a predator.
Ahh... Huh?!
Sorry, Sasuke..
Naruto!
The password... I forgot it!
hey, can you hear it?
nee kikoe masu ka
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
the clear, blue sky goes on and on
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
the ocean spans limitlessly
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
please keep that smile on your face forever
janai to nai chau kara
or else I'll cry
mawari o mimawasa naku temo
You won't have to search around you
mou iin da yo
it's all ok now
kono to no naka ni wa minna ga iru kara
everyone is inside this hand
naki taku natte nige taku natte
when you want to cry, and you want to run away
shiawase o wasure te te shimatta ra
when you forget what happiness is
mina utae
just sing
hikari ga umare yami ga umare ta
light is born, and darkness was born
futatsu wa hitotsu
the two are one
HARUMONIA kanji Te TEREPASHII
harmonia, feel the telepathy
nee kikoe masu ka
hey, can you hear it?
Hey, hey, hey!
It looks like you bullied
weaklings while I was gone.
That explosion and
that huge snake,
it's all your fault, isn't it?
You damn snake bastard!
Now that I, Uzumaki Naruto-sama, is here,
I'll wipe the floor with you!
Next episode:
"Naruto Strikes Back! I'm Not Going to Run Away!"
Look forward to my kicking butt!